motoroids.com 2018-03-30

# Privacy Policy | Motoroids

At Motoroids.com (“Website”), we strongly believe in protecting the privacy of the personal information of our readers, and in using it only in ways that have been notified to you. This Privacy Policy is a legal document which explains the extent of personal information we collect from you and where it would be used, the steps we take to ensure your security, who we may share it with and how can you correct or remove your information from our database.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact us at feedback@motoroids.com

Kindly read the detailed policy below:

Motoroids respects your privacy and recognizes the need to guard the personally identifiable information (any information by which you can be identified, such as name, address, and telephone number) you share with us. We would like to declare that we follow suitable standards when it comes to shielding your privacy on our Website.

You can visit the Website without disclosing your identity or revealing any personal information about yourself. We track the Internet address of the domains from you may visit us and analyze this data for better understanding our visitors.

A few of our pages use cookies to enable us to customize your experience. Cookies are sent to your browser by the website to improve your experience during your next visit. You can set your browser to update you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the option to make a decision whether or not to accept it. This information is primarily used to improve our service to you.

Some times we may collect personal information which you have volunteered to provide to us (or “opted in” for), such as name, physical address or telephone number, email address, mobile number etc. At any such time, we will inform you the reason for this information being collected and promise to utilize it for only that particular purpose. It will always be optional for you to provide the information, and you can always opt out of certain uses of the information. If you decide not to provide the information we require in certain sections of the website, you can still visit the Website, but you may be unable to access certain options and services.

Motoroids will take all the required steps to protect the information you share with us. We have implemented security features to safeguard the privacy of your information from unauthorized access and improper use or disclosure.

Motoroids will never sell and disclose any information derived from the registration for, or use of, any online service to third parties without the consent of the user. We may however use your information to provide you a personalized experience, improve our site, get in touch with you if necessary and provide you services.

By continuing to use Motoroids or by continuing to remain registered with us, you hereby agree that you have read and understood the terms of use and the privacy policy. Changes in our Privacy Policy will be updated here and you are requested to keep yourself updated with the changes. Motoroids Web Private Limited will under no circumstances be liable for any loss, damage etc caused to you.

This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology Act, 2000. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.
